(Howard:)Pasty and frail, never fail.
(Leonard:)Excuse me, but what about me?
(Leonard:)Why don't I get a shot?
(Howard:)Fine, go ahead, take a shot.
(Leonard:)I've already got a gorgeous blonde
back home I can't score with.
(Leonard:)I think I'll let you two take this one.
(Raj:)Sheldon, is there a place on this train
to get alcohol?
(Sheldon:)Interesting that you ask.
(Sheldon:)The Coast Starlight recently added
the refurbished Pacific Parlour Car.
(Sheldon:)Built in 1956 and originally known as
the Santa Fe Lounge Car, the lower level...
(Raj:)- Which way?
- Upper level is a bar...
(Sheldon:)...that offers wine tastings
if you're going as far as Portland.
Aren't you gonna go talk to her?
(Sheldon:)I will.
I'm just working on my opening line.
(Leonard:)She's probably heard every possible line,
Howard.
Why don't you try, "Hello?"
(Howard:)No, no, no.
That always creeps girls out.
(Howard:)I need to come up with something that's
funny, smart and delicately suggests...
(Howard:)...that my sexual endowment
is disproportionate to my physical stature.
You're gonna need more than 11 hours.